<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<activity id="251763" moduleid="1780209" modulename="page" contextid="2777094">
  <page id="251763">
    <name>Preparing Your Online Course</name>
    <intro></intro>
    <introformat>1</introformat>
    <content>&lt;p&gt;After you request a copy of your course for a new term, there will be a few maintenance and setup tasks that wil need to be completed before the course is ready for students. This document aims to help you complete these tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you have not already requested a new course, and you are currently viewing a previous offering of the course, you can request that a new course site is created using the &lt;a href="https://courserequest.learn.illinois.edu/" target="_blank"&gt;Course Request System&lt;/a&gt;. More information about the Course Request System can be found on the &lt;a href="http://go.illinois.edu/moodlecourserequest" target="_blank"&gt;Requesting a Course Site page&lt;/a&gt;. Please note that the Course Request System includes a convenient dates rollover function that you can check to have the date settings for quizzes and other assignments adjusted for the requested copy of your course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Course Cleanup&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; Depending on the number of weeks in your course, you may need to add or remove weeks from your course shell. You can remove or add sections by using the "Edit settings" page under the "Course administration" drop-down menu in the course navigation located on the left side of the course site. Under the "Course Format" drop-down, adjust the "Number of sections" field to remove any blank sections in your course. For more infomation about these settings you can view the &lt;a href="http://go.illinois.edu/moodlecoursesettings" target="_blank"&gt;Course Settings page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; Also located on the "Edit settings" page for the course is the "Course start date." If this is not accurate, update it here and save the settings by clicking the save button at the bottom of the page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt;If you need to add any users to your course that are not included in the course roster (e.g. TAs), you can add them manually. This is done from the "Users" drop-down under "Course administration". Click the link for "Enrolled users". If you need further instruction on adding a user, check out the &lt;a href="http://go.illinois.edu/moodleaddusers" target="_blank"&gt;Adding Users page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Course Rollover&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Updating Basic Page Content&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt;Your couse will utilize several pages that display textual information. Some of these pages will contain information that will need to be updated each term. For example, if you are new to teaching the course, you will want to update the course with your contact information; most often, this is located in an Instructor Information page. There will also be pages that have text including due dates for assignments, these will need to be updated as well. Look out for dates in the Syllabus, Calendar, Exam Information, Course Orientation, and Weekly Overview pages. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your course will likely not include all these pages, but do check those which are included in your course&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. For pages that require editing, you can learn how to use the editor on the &lt;a href="http://go.illinois.edu/moodletexteditor" target="_blank"&gt;Moodle Text Editor page&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Adjusting Dates&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; The &lt;a href="https://courserequest.learn.illinois.edu/"&gt;Course Request System&lt;/a&gt; includes a convenient dates rollover function you can use to have the date settings for quizzes and other assignments adjusted for the requested copy of your course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; If you need to rollover your dates but did not request a dates rollover when you requested your course copy, then you can contact &lt;a href="mailto:atlas-tlt@illinois.edu" target="_blank"&gt;ATLAS-TLT@illinois.edu&lt;/a&gt; for assistance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Group Creation&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt;Learn@Illinois allows instructors to divide students who are enrolled into their course into groups and groupings. The groups feature allows groups of students to work more closely with one another and also provides instructors with some administrative capabilities, especially in large course that are divided into sections. The groupings feature also allows activities to be restricted to a particular grouping. This could be useful for large courses in which individual sections have separate activities. Keep in mind that there are only two levels, groups and groupings. You can create the effect of a tertiary level by creating another set of groups and grouping. Learn more about groups and groupings from the &lt;a href="http://go.illinois.edu/moodlegroups" target="_blank"&gt;Groups and Groupings&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;E-reserves&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; If your course uses Electronic Reserve items from the library, these will need to be copied in the &lt;a href="https://reserves.library.illinois.edu/ares/" target="_blank"&gt;E-Reserves System&lt;/a&gt;. For instructions on how to copy items from a previous course, see the &lt;a href="http://guides.library.illinois.edu/reserves/reuse" target="_blank"&gt;Reusing Reserves&lt;/a&gt; page from the library. If you have questions about using the E-Reserves System, contact Collection Management Services at &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer nofollow" class="link" data-attrib-id="MTQ1OTQ1Mjk4NTg0MC1tYWlsdG86Y21zZXJ2aWNlc0BsaWJyYXJ5LmlsbGlub2lzLmVkdQ==" href="mailto:cmservices@library.illinois.edu"&gt;cmservices@library.illinois.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Collaborate&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; If your course uses Collaborate sessions for &lt;span class="nolink"&gt;Virtual Office, Study Lounge, or Live Sessions&lt;/span&gt;, they will all need to be re-created for the new term. To create a session, click the link for "Add an activity or resource" in the section you wish to add the session, select "Blackboard Collaborate" from the activities list and click the "Add" button. For further instructions on setting up Collaborate sessions see the &lt;a href="http://go.illinois.edu/moodlecollaboratesetup" target="_blank"&gt;Blackboard Collaborate page&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that for virtual offices you will want to set the recording to "manual."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span class="nolink"&gt;Final Exam&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This course template provides an empty Final Exam in Week 8 that you can use to create your &lt;span class="nolink"&gt;Final Exam&lt;/span&gt; or other exams in your course (e.g., Midterm Exam, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; Before you can deploy your Final Exam, you need to set a number of options to control the exam's behavior, such as the opening and closing dates/times, the time limit, whether a password is required, what sort of feedback students get and when, etc. For instructions on how to control the exam settings, please see the &lt;a href="http://go.illinois.edu/moodlequizsetup" target="_blank"&gt;Moodle Quiz documentation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; Once you have created the initial exam settings, and provided you do not wish to change or add any other settings, you will only need to update the opening and closing time setting options in future iterations of the course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; Proctored exams should use a password. You can add a password requirement using the "Extra Restriction on Attempts" option of the exam settings. See also the &lt;strong&gt;ProctorU&lt;/strong&gt; instructions on this page if your course uses the ProctorU service for online proctored exams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;ProctorU&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; If your course uses the ProctorU service for online proctored exams, your course syllabus will typically say so. If your course uses ProctorU exams, you will need to schedule exam windows with ProctorU so your students can sign up for an online proctored exam appointment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; Before you can set up exams in the ProctorU scheduling system, you must first complete the &lt;a href="http://go.illinois.edu/proctoruguidelines" target="_blank"&gt;ProctorU Instructor Guidelines and Acknowledgment&lt;/a&gt;. Completing this online form will also provide you with the required access and training you need to use the ProctorU scheduling system to set up exams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; For general information about ProctorU, see the &lt;a href="https://learn.illinois.edu/http:/go.illinois.edu/online-proctoring" target="_blank"&gt;ProctorU Overview&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Extended Testing Time and Deadline Exceptions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; You may receive one or more formal DRES accommodation notices from students who require additional testing time. The letter will state how much additional testing time is required. 1.5x extended testing time, for example, would mean that student would get 90 minutes for a 60-minute exam. To add extended time for individual students, please see the Moodle instructions for &lt;a href="http://go.illinois.edu/moodleoverride" target="_blank"&gt;Giving Students Extra Time or Attempts on a Quiz&lt;/a&gt;. Note that this over ride setting can also be used to provide early/late access to a quiz or exam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Ensemble&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt; If your course uses an Ensemble video repository, you can request upload access for adding new videos by emailing &lt;a href="mailto:moran@illinois.edu"&gt;moran@illinois.edu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Releasing the Course&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt;When you are ready to un-hide the course from students you can do so by following the instructions on the &lt;a href="http://publish.illinois.edu/atlas-tlt/2014-fall-instructor-help/making-course-sites-visible/#moreinfo2" target="_blank"&gt;Making Course Sites Visible page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;input type="checkbox" /&gt;After the course is visible to students, it is recommended that you send a 'welcome announcment' by making a post in the Announcements forum (sometimes called "News forum"). For instructions on how to post to this forum, check out the &lt;a href="http://publish.illinois.edu/atlas-tlt/2014-fall-instructor-help/making-announcements/" target="_blank"&gt;Making Announcments page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <contentformat>1</contentformat>
    <legacyfiles>0</legacyfiles>
    <legacyfileslast>$@NULL@$</legacyfileslast>
    <display>5</display>
    <displayoptions>a:2:{s:12:"printheading";s:1:"1";s:10:"printintro";s:1:"0";}</displayoptions>
    <revision>9</revision>
    <timemodified>1478295081</timemodified>
  </page>
</activity>